<resources>
    
     <string name="about">

        \n<b><u>The Purpose</u></b>\n\nThe developments in the fields of <b>atomic energy</b> and <b>ionising radiations</b> have shown that they can provide immense benefit
        to mankind. Their use in different facets of our life is rapidly increasing. <b>However</b>, these technologies are also
        facing a serious problem, a problem of perception. Most of the Indians are completely blinded by the negative effects of these. There is also a growing fear in the minds of the public about the harmful effects
        of ionising radiation.\nThe fear could be due to incomplete knowledge and may not have any scientific basis. In any case, if the <b>utilisation</b> of atomic energy and ionising radiations is to gain public acceptance,
        it is essential that all the information about these subjects is made amply available to the common man,
        in a language he understands. It is recognised that for an <b>optimum utilization</b> of any technology, a comprehensive
        appreciation of its problems and potentials must prevail not only amongst the scientists and engineers associated
        with the technology but amongst the general public also. In the case of ionising radiations while its <b>hazard
        aspects</b> seem to have been over played for historial or other reasons, its full potential in the service of
        mankind does not seem to have drawn the deserved attention of the general public. \n\n

        <b><u>How this App will help</u></b>\n\nThis <b>Mobile Application</b> can be used as a <b>tool to educate</b> the general public that we live in a Radioactive world,
        and Radiation has always been all around us as a part of our natural environment.\nIt will be shown that the amount of radiation that we receive from a nuclear power plant is much <b>less</b> than the amount
        of radiation that we receive as a result of cosmic radiation, presence of <b>Radon in air</b>, etc. This will help in reducing irrational fear of nuclear radiation to some extend Indian Public.
    </string>

    <string name="app_name">PRDC</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="graph_info">NS- Natural Sources\nWYL- Where You Live\nRN- Radon\nEA- Consumption and Air</string>
</resources>
